<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<SPICES>
    <SPICE>
        <SPICE_ALLERGEN_INFORMATION>None Specified</SPICE_ALLERGEN_INFORMATION>
        <SPICE_BASIC_APPLICATION>Rule of thumb, 1 oz. of dry mushrooms reconstitutes to 3-4 oz. of fresh mushrooms. To prepare, start by rinsing the product in cold, running water to remove any debris. To reconstitute, put the desired amount of mushrooms to be used in a bowl, cover with boiling water and then let them soak for 25 minutes prior to draining.</SPICE_BASIC_APPLICATION>
        <SPICE_CUISINE>Asian, Chinese, European, French</SPICE_CUISINE>
        <SPICE_DESCRIPTION>These shredded Wood Ear mushrooms look like destroyed confidential files from a government office rather than food. Perhaps under all that black you might find some undisclosed secret kept hidden from the public.But no, these are mushrooms. Hydrated, these delicate strings of finely sliced Wood Ear mushroom become brown and crunchy with a forest-y flavor.Many chefs have begun to treat shredded Wood Ear like a pasta as instead of a mushroom. Add them to cold soba dishes, or tangle together with fettuccini and slather in an alfredo sauce for an East-meets-West dish. We like to add them into a chicken soup for their antiviral properties. Curious in texture, intriguing in flavor, and with a contemporary appearance this mushroom is perfect for the hip home cook.</SPICE_DESCRIPTION>
        <SPICE_DIETARY_PREFERENCES>All Natural, Gluten-Free, Kosher Parve, Non-GMO</SPICE_DIETARY_PREFERENCES>
        <SPICE_HANDLING_AND_STORAGE>Store in a cool, dry place.</SPICE_HANDLING_AND_STORAGE>
        <SPICE_INGREDIENTS>Dried wood ear mushrooms.</SPICE_INGREDIENTS>
        <SPICE_INTRO>An adorable, tangled nest of mushroom. Long ribbons of Wood Ear that are darling to look at and more so to eat. Add to pasta dishes as crunchy noodles of earthy goodness. Toss in stir-fries to tie up loose chiles or sop up fermented black bean sauce.</SPICE_INTRO>
        <SPICE_LINKS>https://www.spicejungle.com/wood-ear-mushrooms-shredded</SPICE_LINKS>
        <SPICE_NAME>Wood Ear Mushrooms, Shredded</SPICE_NAME>
        <SPICE_COUNTRY_ORIGIN>China</SPICE_COUNTRY_ORIGIN>
        <SPICE_PRODUCT_STYLE>Shredded</SPICE_PRODUCT_STYLE>
        <SPICE_RECOMMENDED_APPLICATION>Crunch and mildly flavored, this popular mushroom is traditionally used in many Oriental soups. Can be used with most meats but are exceptionally complimentary with pork recipes.</SPICE_RECOMMENDED_APPLICATION>
    </SPICE>
    <SPICE>
        <SPICE_ALLERGEN_INFORMATION>Contains sulfites</SPICE_ALLERGEN_INFORMATION>
        <SPICE_BASIC_APPLICATION>No preparation necessary, ready to use as is. To reconstitute to the flavor of table Worcestershire, blend 1 part Worcestershire Powder to 1.5 parts water (by weight).</SPICE_BASIC_APPLICATION>
        <SPICE_CUISINE>American, Australian, British, Canadian, Indonesian, Mexican, Thai</SPICE_CUISINE>
        <SPICE_DESCRIPTION>An accidental discovery, the first Worcestershire sauce was made in Worcester England, by John Wheeley Lea and William Perrins, a couple of pharmacists with a eye for culinary intrigue. Originally, the sauce was sold as both a flavoring and a digestive agent.The sauce in question was actually a British attempt to recreate a fermented fish sauce called garum, a popular flavoring used in Italy and Greece. The anchovy-based recipe was flavored with tamarind, cloves, malt vinegar, onion, molasses, and other ingredients. However, the resulting sauce was so completely inedible that the remaining barrels were shelved aside. After time, however, the sauce had mellowed and fermented taking on a lovely flavor.And that is Worcestershire sauce.This sauce is just that, but it’s been dehydrated and into a significantly more potent Worcestershire seasoning. Worcestershire powder can be mixed with water to form a quick sauce, but we also love it in rubs for ribs or sprinkled onto a steak or ham during the last bits of cooking so it can form a Worcestershire glaze.</SPICE_DESCRIPTION>
        <SPICE_DIETARY_PREFERENCES>Gluten-Free, Kosher Parve</SPICE_DIETARY_PREFERENCES>
        <SPICE_HANDLING_AND_STORAGE>Store in a cool, dry place.</SPICE_HANDLING_AND_STORAGE>
        <SPICE_INGREDIENTS>Maltodextrin, Worcestershire Sauce (Distilled Vinegar, Molasses, Corn Syrup, Salt, Caramel Color, Garlic Powder, Sugar, Spices, Tamarind, Natural Flavor. Contains Sulfites), Silicon Dioxide. This product contains bioengineered ingredients.</SPICE_INGREDIENTS>
        <SPICE_INTRO>Can sheer manliness have a flavor? We think so.</SPICE_INTRO>
        <SPICE_LINKS>https://www.spicejungle.com/worcestershire-sauce-powder</SPICE_LINKS>
        <SPICE_NAME>Worcestershire Sauce Powder</SPICE_NAME>
        <SPICE_COUNTRY_ORIGIN>United States</SPICE_COUNTRY_ORIGIN>
        <SPICE_PRODUCT_STYLE>Powder</SPICE_PRODUCT_STYLE>
        <SPICE_RECOMMENDED_APPLICATION>Add Worcestershire Powder to flavor sauce, stews, or soups. Worcestershire Sauce Powder is a versatile spice, try experimenting with this powder with other herbs and spices to create your very own dry rub, or simply sprinkle on cooked steaks, pork, or roasts for great flavor. Sprinkle on pasta or steamed vegetables or mix in with your parmesan cheese prior to adding to your dish.</SPICE_RECOMMENDED_APPLICATION>
    </SPICE>
    <SPICE>
        <SPICE_ALLERGEN_INFORMATION>Contains sesame seeds</SPICE_ALLERGEN_INFORMATION>
        <SPICE_BASIC_APPLICATION>Ready to use as is, no preparation is necessary.</SPICE_BASIC_APPLICATION>
        <SPICE_CUISINE>Iranian, Middle Eastern, North African, Turkish</SPICE_CUISINE>
        <SPICE_DESCRIPTION>Zaatar spice is the name of both a popular seasoning and herbal shrub found in the Middle East. Obviously, we're here to talk about the seasoning. Za atar is a zesty, sour, nutty spice blend that owes much of its flavor to sumac and to toasted sesame seeds. Salt is often added, but from there on it really depends on who is making it. Some commercial varieties also include roasted flour. Our blend comes with oregano and thyme to create an overly herbal salty-sour mix with plenty of earthiness from the sesame.Zaatar spice mix is often enjoyed as a condiment. Dip bread in your favorite olive oil, and then dip into a bowl of Zaatar for an easy appetizer with zing. Whip into butter, ricotta, or sour cream for tangy spread and dips. If you plan to make your own French fries or potato chips, sprinkle them with Zaatar once they finish cooking for a fragrant snack.</SPICE_DESCRIPTION>
        <SPICE_HANDLING_AND_STORAGE>Store in a cool, dry place.</SPICE_HANDLING_AND_STORAGE>
        <SPICE_INGREDIENTS>Ground sumac, spices, sesame seed, salt and canola oil. Contains Sesame.</SPICE_INGREDIENTS>
        <SPICE_INTRO>Zaatar spice is the name of both a popular seasoning and herbal shrub found in the Middle East. Obviously, we're here to talk about the seasoning. Za atar is a zesty, sour, nutty spice blend that owes much of its flavor to sumac and to toasted sesame seeds. Salt is often added, but from there on it really depends on who is making it. Some commercial varieties also include roasted flour. Our blend comes with oregano and thyme to create an overly herbal salty-sour mix with plenty of earthiness from the sesame.</SPICE_INTRO>
        <SPICE_LINKS>https://www.spicejungle.com/zaatar-spice-blend</SPICE_LINKS>
        <SPICE_NAME>Zaatar Spice</SPICE_NAME>
        <SPICE_COUNTRY_ORIGIN>United States</SPICE_COUNTRY_ORIGIN>
        <SPICE_PRODUCT_STYLE>Powder</SPICE_PRODUCT_STYLE>
        <SPICE_RECOMMENDED_APPLICATION>Use Zahtar spice with grilled, roasted, or stewed potatoes, vegetables, fish, chicken or lamb. Create a sandwich spread by mixing za atar seasoning with mayo, cream cheese or olive oil. Add to a marinade, salad dressing, yogurt, or hummus for extra flavor.</SPICE_RECOMMENDED_APPLICATION>
    </SPICE>
</SPICES>
